// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "which keyword is used for debbuging in Java?",
    answer: "Assert",
    options: [
      "Abstract",
      "Insert",
      "Assert",
      "Boolean"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "what is the use of javac command",
    answer: "Compile a java program",
    options: [
      "Execute a java program",
      "Debug a java program",
      "Interpret a java program",
      "Compile a java program"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who invented Java Programming?",
    answer: "James Gosling",
    options: [
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "James Gosling",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Bjarne Stroustrup"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which component is used to compile,debug and execute the java programming?",
    answer: "JDK",
    options: [
      "JRE",
      "JIT",
      "JVM",
      "JDK"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of these cannot be used for a variable name in Java?",
    answer: "Keywords",
    options: [
      "identifiers & Keywords",
      "Keywords",
      "identifiers",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which of the following is not in OOPS concept in Java",
     answer: "Compilation",
     options: [
       "Polymorphism",
       "Inheritance",
       "Compilation",
       "Encapsulation"
     ]
   },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory",
    answer: "Out of MemoryError",
    options: [
      "MemoryError",
      "MemoryOutofBOundsException",
      "MemoryFullException",
      "Out of MemoryError"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these are selection statements in Java?",
    answer: "if()",
    options: [
      "for()",
      "if()",
      "continue",
      "break"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
    answer: "Object class",
    options: [
      "Object class",
      "Abstract class",
      "ArrayList",
      "string"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "check",
      "throw",
      "catch",
      "try"
    ]
  },

]